↑↑Connection relics!
Everyone, I'm already with you!
Boo-boo, here you go.
If you follow me, I'll take this away from you.
Yeah, it's decided that this time we're going to send you from Ima-san's house, Yokohama Arena, Yokohama Arena.
Yokohama Arena Yokohama Arena this time, right?
The live concert will start in a few minutes, but today is the last day of the concert, right?
I'll see you again before Akimoto's graduation live starts!
I couldn't get on the plane to turn it down... and before that I was on location for work in Hokkaido... and I jumped in and it turned out to be a bit of a disaster.
I'm looking forward to it.
We're going to start the live show with the Eleven Water and Bus.
Nogizaka46's 11th birthday live at Yokohama Arena!
The live was followed by the new generation's farewell live.
The last day of the event, the graduation concert of Manatsu Akimoto, attracted a total of 60,000 fans and even more on the live streaming.
Tonight, Bananaman will report on the situation just before the 5th day and look back on the birthday live.
And the last present for Akimoto, who is graduating...
So, since we didn't feel comfortable with just the two of us, we asked these two to join us.
Tomio Umezawa, Tomio Umezawa and Atsushi Tamura.
Atsushi Tamura... and Umezawa and Mio Umezawa...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Umezawa and Tamura are here.
What pajamas did you bring? Goods.
What's this? Designed by Manatsu-san?
I think so.
She's wearing the Mannequin uniform. Is this what they're selling this time?
Yes, they're for sale. We have a block.
There's also a block.
You mean Akimoto's? Akimoto's? I see. You mean the bottom one is yours?
So you mean the bottom part is your own? The bottom part is your own.
Are you still going to the show with this? No, that's not it.
No, that's not it. Yes, it's a rehearsal. - A rehearsal?
Really? You're going to do it today? Yes, it's a bloodbath.
We'll do it. We'll do it.
We'll do it or we won't. We'll do it or we won't.
I'll make sure not to show you. What's this concert?
It's a storytelling space. It's Akimoto Manatsu's graduation concert.
Is that for today? Yes, it's different every day.
Who's making these? Are the staff doing it?
I think so. Let's take a picture.
What's this? This is called Mochi.
It's a character of your idea. - Oh, really?
It's Mochi. I think it's Mochi.
You haven't been very careful with it? I heard this was made into a product.
Let's take a picture of this. It's Akimoto. Akimoto, what's this?
This is from a fan? Yes, from a fan.
Fans made this for us. Amazing!
This Akimoto is life-size, right? No, it's too big.
This one's maybe 5 or 6 meters.
Is this Akimoto's head like this?
No, no, no, I think it's much smaller.
Down a little bit? It's more like a zing.
He's cute. He's cute.
It smells good in here. This is the catering area.
Did you have something to drink? I had coffee.
I had a matcha latte.
What? Here comes Hayashi!
Suzuki's here. Did he announce it, too?
When was it? March 28th.
Suzuki, this is your last big show, right?
I see. And you, Asari...
Are you in it? It's the first one, so it's approved.
Is it approved? I did the live diary on the second day.
Alone? And in between, alone?
There's no daylight savings.
I see you're wearing black pants, Daikon.
Are they all black? The top's the same.
Why? Is it a trend?
Is there anything other than black and white?
No, no, I don't care what's underneath.
Hime's style is the same.
I'm sure! I'm black and white too.
Ms. Hime, I was thinking of the fat kid from the Addams Family.
People coordinate.
I'm not conscious of it, it just happens when I change my clothes.
Soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Cafe space
Catering.
Before that, Mr. Daikon, you were weak.
Wait a minute. Sorry.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Hime's then?
Is this a weakling's feather?
Is it from Hime's picture?
Yes!
You'd be surprised what you can get away with.
I was so surprised.
I was so surprised when Hime stopped me.
Surprise!
I didn't think you'd go through with it.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
And this one? There it is.
Look, they're different.
But they're both collectibles.
Is this one of them?
Is that black?
Yes, different color.
Oh, really?
It's a T-shirt.
Is it out? Are you okay?
Are you making a scene?What's going on?
I've never seen backyard walnuts before.
Backyard walnuts.
They're causing a ruckus today.
The emergency belt must've been pushed down, right? Suddenly.
It's going to be...
Oh, my God.
The big show.
Today? What's the big reveal?
Can I give you a hint?
Give me a hint.
Give me one more hint. I don't know.
I know about the apartment.
I know you're singing about the apartment.
Are you singing about an apartment?
You and your clothes are pretty much the same color.
What do you mean?
Oh...
It's a sickle-cutter.
Wait a minute.
Seriously? You're gonna get it with a scythe cutter?
Maybe.
The sickle-cutting's really funny this time.
We're finally getting a sickle-cutter.
We did it.
What's up with that?
This first one is too cute.
A little more of the sickle-cut.
That way it's easier to see.
They're catching and eating all the members.
I wonder if they're all green.
I wonder...
I don't know.
You did it, finally.
Manatsu-san is teaching me how to use my hands.
What? Why is Akimoto floating?
I'm instructing Kamaki.
No, no, no. What does she know about Kamaki?
I don't know... Manatsu-san knows more about him than me.
She's very particular about Kamaki.
I've never heard of it.
Six seconds ago, I was wondering what he was talking about.
What did he say?
"Let's turn your hands a little more this way.
Yes, like this.
So cute! So cute!
You're doing the kamakiri, you can't turn your head out a little more.
The height, the expression, everything.
All the way down to the expression.
You have to have that student look on your face.
I want to see that face.
The inverted triangle.
That's right. That's what we're here to see.
Manatsu-san...
That's right, that's what they're here to see, guys.
It's so important, it's a character, they're going to take a picture of it
It's important, this Kamakiri character
Kamagiri character
Hime-san, in the old days, people used to use cameras and...
Camel...
Wait a minute. Are you sure you want to spend this much time?
Here...
I thought it was important to teach Kamaguri.
Then let's move on.
Let's move forward.
What's this space for?
Oh, food.
Looks good.
It's a hamburger!
More rice, normal, less rice, none
It's hard to ask for more rice.
Idols don't have more, more or less.
Here it comes again.
Already here.
Black version.
See, I knew Yamamoto wouldn't wear something like this.
No, I have some at home.
If I don't wear it here...
I'll come dress you.
There's no time.
Are you sure you didn't spill it? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I don't know if that counts as a spill.
What happened?
When I was pouring the hot water out of the pot.
I missed the whole thing the first time.
How did you do that?
Really?
Why did you do that?
I got a flower.
Why?
Because it's already here.
It's already here.
Why is it off?
Isn't it time you spilled it?
It came off.
I couldn't get a drop in.
So I moved it.
And then it came off again. All of it.Then it came off again. All of it.
Why?
So I soaked it once already.
Oh, this is it, isn't it?
What do you mean?
You're supposed to take it off like this, right here.
That's the type of thing you do.
No, no, no, no. There's no way to get it off.
And what do you mean, it's coming off fine?
And it's boiling water, so it's bad, right?
You're supposed to put it down like this.
Why would you put it down?
Because it's coming off.
I did it and it came off.
Try it. It'll definitely come off there.
Here, it's unlocked.
Unlocked.
I almost did it myself.
Do it.
It's gonna come off here.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
It's too hot.
They say it'll come off.
It'll come off.
They're supposed to hold it.
Why do they take it off?
Just hold it.
Hold it?
You're not gonna put it down.
We're all gonna have it.
I'll hold it. I'll hold it.
We're not a 7-Eleven convenience store.
I've learned my lesson.
That's right.
You do this kind of thing?
I'll count it as a spill.
I didn't spill it, but...
I spilled it.
That's funny.
Be careful on the set.
You okay? - Yeah.
Don't drop the mike or anything.
I'm fine.
That's the proper thing to say.
Now that you say it like you mean it.
I'm talking to you, aren't I?
What's all right?
It's not okay.
Of course not.
I'm sure it's off and on.
Why don't you just say "off and on"?
When do you make the sound?
Oh, my God, it's a Krupner toy!
Oh, my God, it's a Krupner toy.
Did you brush your teeth?
I brushed my teeth.
How did you brush your teeth?
Not just my teeth.
I'm sitting next to you today.
When you drink miso soup, your elbows are like this.
You're in my way.
You're really in the way.
Why do you make that face?
Only we'll know.
Then do something.
Oh, that's good.
Wow, that's not easy.
For the show.
I'm not gonna say anything weird.
I don't know.
Why don't you touch your teeth?
I want to be in pain.
I'm tantanizing people. I'm riding with people.
What do you mean, like, tooth-bashing?
I'm gonna get tongue in my nose after you hit my teeth.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't think I can do that at the moment.
You're gonna get it all over your face.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no. That's not what I meant.
But I hope it's a good time.
Good luck with that.
You want to keep going?
I'm already over there.
I can't go this way.
I can't go this way either?
No, today.
Good luck with that.
I can't go this way.
Good luck.
I don't think we're allowed to go from here to here.
Oh, there's something around here.
Delicious local snacks.
That's right.
Agi no Tsuki
Well, well, well...Well, well, well.
It's a manjuu, isn't it?
You're always talking about manjuu.
You know what a manjuu is.
It's not that I don't know anything about manjuu.
You know what I mean.
I don't know what a manjuu is.
That's a manjuu, isn't it?
What manjuu?
What is this playing?
YouTube?
YouTube.
We have YouTube buns.
It's a YouTube bun.
You're on YouTube?
Nogizaka YouTube.
Nogizaka YouTube!
That's the official YouTube.
They're streaming "Kensetsu-zhunaka" too.
That's right.
You know it?
Yes, yes, yes.
No, I don't.
I never watch YouTube.
Yes, yes, yes.
We also do a lot of projects.
We do a lot of projects.
I think we're doing a YouTube project.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Not at all.
Let's not talk about that anymore.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Photo Spot.
Who's there?
Gokisei!
Gokisei-chan is here.
Gokisei-chan
Oh, Irokkusi-yan!
You did the Kibei live, didn't you?
We did!
It was amazing!
That was your first time doing that voice.
Yes, it was.
It's the first time I've been allowed to do that.
First time?
How was it?
I was happy to hear my name read like this.
It made me happy.
I was.
The moment I walked in, everyone was so ticklish.
They were all like this.
That was Kaede.
You don't know how wide it is?
It's like a live performance.
There was a cheer.
It's like a cheer.
No, no, no.
It's a little bit no good
They call me Shokichi.
Like a towel.
There's a towel
In my house or something...
Shokichi
Shigawara Masayoshi
Seriously
Masayoshi Shigawara
When we perform as a whole, I'm often at the end of the stage while the senior dancers are dancing.
I'm often at the very end of the stage.
I often feel embarrassed and ashamed.
I see.
Frequently.
I'm sorry about that.
It's a good thing that your character is well known.
Today is Akimoto's graduation live.
Have you seen Akimoto? Today.
Yes, I did.
What was Akimoto's mood like?
She's making fun of me.
He's making fun of you, Yuna.
I thought you were right.
I don't know.
I'm not sure if it's right for me anymore.
We've been rehearsing since early morning.
Poor Yuna.
Everyone's making fun of her and laughing.
I don't know... maybe I don't fit in.
We're backstage together, too.
What's up with that?
Don't be silly.
Good luck.
Good luck!
You're so popular!
Which season do you think is the most popular?
Awkward!
What kind of question is that?
Which term do you think is the most popular?
The third term, of course
Yes.
Which childWhich child
I think it's the fourth term.
I'll take that as a yes.
Where do you think?
That's very bold... a fifth term.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But I'm not sure I feel the same way.
We're all Nogizaka.
That's right.
There's a lot of them.
What's with that?
We can't see them there, but...
But when they come out here, they can all meet.
That's so cool, it's like a free kick.
Line 'em up, line 'em up, line 'em up, line 'em up.
I've got your permission.
Okay, let's go over there.
Okay, let's go there.
Thanks.
Everyone's wearing different clothes over here.
They're all wearing this today.
Oh, you're wearing it?
You're wearing this?
This one too
And this one, too.
This is the birthday line
This is really something
Birthday line
This one looks like it could be worn in everyday life.
No, this one's great. I mean, they're all great.
This one's good, too.
I've been asking everyone what they think of it.
TRF, right?
TRF!
TRF's not playing.
Put it on the back.
You're not gonna play TRF?
No, no, no, no, they're not playing.
It's not TRF.
I've been telling everyone for a while now.
They're going to touch Akimoto's teeth.
There's a tooth challenge.
I didn't do that.
During the show, I touched Akimoto's teeth.
I'm going to touch the bridge of his nose.
If there's a chance to do it, I'll do it.
There is an opening, but you can't do it.
Pit!
He's going to get all frizzy.
I'm not getting crumpled up.
No, no, no, no. No matter how many times he comes near you, he'll get crumpled.
What idol?
That's what idols are for!
Then I'll give him more pew pew pew pew.
He's got a lot of openings, and he's getting hit hard.
He's probably at his best when he's MCing.
But you're the new captain... the new captain!
Congratulations!
There he is, the big captain.
That's a lot of work.
Umeda-san, why don't you pick five new captains?
Then we'll all go together.
Clothes? All these clothes?
If we just pick clothes, we'll have to pick an insurance guy and everything.
Insurance... that's a good idea.
I was in the choir in middle school.
What's a choreographer?
Try it.
You're not that familiar with it.
Careful!
I'll do it... this is good... this is Barry.
and just before the show Akimoto appeared on stage to end the show
Thank you very much, it's the same to you... you're eating edarings...
We're eating edaring, aren't we?
I thought we might be having a rehearsal, but I haven't shed that many tears yet.
I thought I might not have cried during the rehearsal, but I haven't cried that many tears yet.
I don't know... it's my decision... and to some extent I'm asking people to do things like this...
I'm a firm believer, so if I have to think about it, I'll do whatever I want.
It's the last time...
I hope she cries a lot
There might be a lot of younger students who'll touch my mom... but I've been trying really hard to stop them.
I'm on a mission to check under the flower that touched my mother...
Or there's a girl who might actually believe it, in which case, I'm going to make sure she doesn't move.
I've got something else I want to give you after I'm done.
Yes, please do your best!
Good luck, welcome!
Go, go, go, go, go!
With Bananaman looking on, the live performance finally started!
The two cheered even more enthusiastically than usual as they watched Akimoto's last heroic performance.
And then, as usual, the descending example was
me
I didn't get that much. I didn't get that much.
This is not the part where laughter breaks out at the "me, me, me, me" moment.
Thank you very much for today, thank you very much!
And Akimoto's graduation live, which lasted over 3 hours, closed with great love
Thank you for your hard work! Wow, here you go!
One Ten Light!One Ten Light!
Good, good, good, good, good, good!
What was that at the end? Triple encore?
What was that ad-libbed?
It was an ad-lib.
I was afraid of what I was going to do.
I thought I'm done for the day... but then they started again.
That was the beginning of the climax, wasn't it?
That's when the excitement really started.
All the grandpas on the trip...
Did you see them?
I could see them!
I could see a lot of people.
It was amazing.
My grandpa was making it so much fun!
Once again, I realized how much Akimoto is loved.
That's why they love her so much.
Why don't you sit down for a minute?
And here's the last talk with Bananaman.
It's going to be a talk, so we started with the part where he suddenly came to see the studio.
I was still a little fuzzy at that point.
His face was so amateurish, in a good way.
Unprofessional.
Freshly boiled.
I know, I know.
The way it was all fluffed up...
It's totally different.
Now it's perfect.
Ripe.
Ripened?
It's too good to be true.
It's like, it's all soft and ripe, and it tastes great.
It's in great shape.
It was great.
Thank you very much.
But it's like the personality that Akimoto created
I think it became the color of Nogizaka
Thank you very much.
I was wondering if Akimoto might be the kind of girl who wouldn't quit.
I was also wondering if she's the kind of person who'd stay on even after 30 years.
Someone who's going to stick around.
Like AKB's Ms. Kajigami.
You know what I mean?
She's always been there.
That's what I thought you might be.
I thought maybe he was quitting.
But in show business.
We'll see each other again.
I have a favor to ask you.
After we graduate... after we graduate...
I'd be happy to work with you.
Can I ask for your contact information?
Of course.
You can ask me now.
No, I can't.
You're making it a rule.
I've got to work hard enough to get this job with you.
Yeah, we're rather starry-eyed.
Stop it.
Stop it!
I'm so old-fashioned, I can't even remember the last time I did that.
No, no, no. Maybe we'll meet soon enough to set a record for the fastest time.
The rest of us.
No, please, please, please.
That's strictly by the rules... when we're in the studio together.
It can be a V-show.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
When we're in the studio together.
It's better to go out on a nonstop spur-of-the-moment basis.
I don't get to see you at all.
Stop that weird one-way traffic.
If it's nonstop, I'll only listen to Shimoda-san.
Then I can go with you at the same time.
There's still a lot of people to greet after this.
A little graduation present from us.
I'm so happy.
Which one do you want first?
I got two. Box.
Box.
The first one.
Oh, my God.
Thank you very much.
The first one.
Oh, wow.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wow.
That's nice.
kosakaya akimoto
I knew it. I knew it. I knew it. I knew it.
I've been saying I want you to do a small restaurant someday
I knew it. Small restaurant Akimoto.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy
I had her wear it over her dress.
You can at least put your sleeves through it.
Yes, ma'am.
It hides the dress.
It's nice.
Here you go.
Akimoto Restaurantsmall restaurant akimoto
Even dresses don't get dirty, so this
Indeed.
I can still cook in this.
No, if you really do a small restaurant, I really want you to wear this.
I'd like to wear it. This...
This is
cool, still no comment.
Thank you
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, okay.
I seriously loved the live music and everything today.
I mean, you did some of the old stuff really well.
That's great.
Wow, that was good.
That was really good.
This one's the main one, I think.
What?
Yeah, get the good stuff.
Helmet.
I got it.
Oh, wow!
Akimoto, a small restaurant
Congrats!
It's pink.
It's my color.
We're going to have a lot of variety, right?
Akimoto, you know, I can't get a helmet.
Well, you know, I had a lot of problems.
She said she wanted to try her hand at variety shows.
So I brought my own helmet.
You wear this every time you go to a variety show.
No, that's right.
You know, you might get held up suddenly.
You might want to bring this with you.
It's just that there's a piece of paper in the back that won't fit.
It's not gonna fit in this.
This will fit.
This is going in, right?
Oh, look.
It'd be great if we could just blow this up or something.
No, and from whom the conglutination.
It's very festive.
It's so stupid.
It's ridiculous.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
My helmet.
This one and this one.
That's great.
It's perfect.
I don't know what's going on.
I don't understand.
After such a great show.
I don't understand why you're dressed like that.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you very much.
We'll see you again.
Thank you so much.
I love your jacket.
No, thank you.
Thank you very much.
The jacket photo of "Hito wa Yume twice" is completed!
Anda live concert will be held!
Started accepting mobile phone orders
Kojibuki pulls
Yes, then
Instant channel registration, song!
Chan chan, subscribe to our channel!
Bye-bye!